Hello everyone, how are
you?  In this video we'll
talk about what
to do if you're
stuck at a stage you
can't pass
, like 6-10, 6-30, or
10-30, you'll definitely
get stuck there, right?  What
I highly recommend is
really simple.  This
video should be
short.  It's very
simple.  I just want to
show you how I
lose and what a
difference it will make between us going forward
.  So, at the last
second we managed to
bring it down to 1%.  Okay.  I
mean, with any luck,
if I just
spam this, we'll
get through easily, right?  But here's
what I'll do
first:
make sure
everything is maxed out
.  Do you see this?    There are
only two levels.
Each level gave 1000
strength.  This is simply
absurd.  That's a
lot.  So
make sure
your entire inventory is
pumped to the
maximum level.
You say, "Soul,
of course, man, I didn't
pump them."  Yes, this is
madness.
Be sure
to level up your
units, because he is on the
list.  Make sure your
units are maxed out
, bro.  Oh my God
.  Okay, that's the first
thing, right?  I'm telling you, you
should
check it out.  These
guys aren't on the
main roster, but
I just
like having
all my SSR units
pumped.  Okay, I'm
wasting my time.  In
any case, the following
is a compilation.
Level it up
as quickly as possible,
gold is the
strongest currency in
this game, and that's why
.  It is literally the
strongest currency.
You say: "Soul,
I already have it pumped
."  I still can't
beat the boss.  I have
leveled up all my
units.  My units are already
at their maximum.  I
just don't have the gold
for it.  Should I just
sit and wait?  Should I
go to the chest?  Should I
take this?  Should I roll
lucky dice?
Of course, friend.  Do
something about it?  All this does
n't matter.
Just get
gold for your account
, you know?  We
received 200 thousand there.
Cool, right?  Pump
these things up.  You get
so much
combat power from it.
You say, "Okay,
I have that."  But I still don't have enough
gold.  I won't
lie, bro, get in
your backpack.  2.9
million.  Get in your
backpack, bro.  Why do we
accumulate resources?
Don't accumulate
anything at the start of the game.
That's ridiculous,
right?  You could even
say it's
counterintuitive, as
rewards
scale
based on your
progress.  Dude, if
you're not moving forward,
why keep them?
It turns out that none of
this
adds up.  You
need to constantly
multiply your
rewards.  This is the
most important thing in life
and in this game.  OK.  One more
point: your
dwarf lab,
focus on it.
I understand that you
want to open
side branches.  But they
take too
much time.  And I'm
not even sure
if you have that currency.
So just don't
waste your time on it.
Maximize it
as soon as possible.
Set an alarm
if you need to
speed up the process with
this currency.
Join a guild.
Make sure
they
help you
pump it up too.
Next is glory.
Glory.  You
will earn this
currency by playing PvP.
You will have to play
PvP.  Just take it
and do it.  It's very
simple.  It's very easy.
You can play at
double speed.
Gain fame.
Get a lot of it.
OK.  Spend it
here.  Next up is the
star connections right
here.  OK.  Your
constellations.  The main goal
here is this.  If
you're too lazy
to read all this, you need to
cover as much
ground as possible.  You see,
I had one lock,
and then I was like, “Oh,
cool.  Now I have
two."  Yes?  To make it
better, if I had
eight here and closed
all of this, it would be just
incredible, right?
It depends on the
composition of your squad.
So when I had 10
units, I could
only activate 10
constellations.  I mean,
I wouldn't have 12 here.
Um, not here.  I wouldn't have
12 here, 11 here,
right?  And you see I
did this when I
only had 11
slots open.  Now I have
12 of them. We can
improve this area.    Will
I do this?
No, because I don't have enough of
this currency.  I only have
310. And when you
fix something, it essentially
makes the rotations
more expensive.  So I could take my
chances, but I don't want to.
In any case, the
main strategy
here is to try
to capture as much
space as possible.  Oh, I wo
n't forgive myself.  I will
do it, but I will do it live
for
you so you can
see and understand
it.  I, I shouldn't
do this.  Okay,
we have one, two.  That's
good.  It's a nice straight
line.  So I could
record a unit
here.  I might as well just
lock in a two
here and just not
worry about that
part of the pie.  It would be
better if I
got a fix of 11
here.  You know what?  We're
just
randomizing again.
Let's see if
we can get off to a
better start.  Oh,
[ __ ], I still
got my
unit fixed.  So, one,
two, three.  This, this is kind of
lame.  We will do it again
.  It's in the middle.
I don't
like it.  This
option is not bad.  We are still
missing out on a lot.
I would rather have an eight.  I
need two
indents, not three where there is
one.  Perfect
.  We have two indentations.
So, we fix
the unit.  I'll fix a two
.  Where did
my threesome go?  This is,
honestly, not bad.
The four is
not bad either.
Everything went wrong on the fifth.  Okay
, the top five was
really bad.
Five, five
wasn't so
bad.  If the six
were here, if the six
were in any of
these places, everything would have
gone better.
Anyway, oh my
god, I'm so sorry I
messed it up.  But you
get the point, right?
You are trying
to cover as much
area as possible.  And yes,
this one has a limit of 10. This one
has a limit of 12. Just
try to get
as much area as possible
after that.  Leave
it alone.  Okay.  One more
thing here.
Raise your cookies.    I have
150 of them. Why do I have
150?  I have no
reason for this.
Although, in fact,
I take my words
back.  The only reason
to have 150 is if I
understand that this cookie is
complete crap, which it is
, and I can
just save
the currency and not mess with
it, right?  and just
wait for the next,
well, limited banner
, which is what I'll probably
do.  I don't
like it because I
just want to spin,
but it totally sucks
.  Indeed so.  But
just, just
spin.  We will
use our
usual summons.
There's no point in
accumulating all these
summons when my
cookies could be
getting stronger.  Uh
, and there's also a collection.  So
, for your gacha
pets,
make sure you
don't hoard these
things.  Try to
get some of the
best pets
available right now.
Honestly, I'm still hunting
for one because I
really like this
"charge".  Oh, if only I could
get it.  It's something
like a
cheesecake.  This is exactly what
we are looking for.  Unfortunately
, two of them.  Oh, just what I
need.  I
needed this.  Oh my God
.  This...wow, we're
getting...this is
really good.  Devil.
Yo, I'm telling you, these
guys are just
crazy.  I
like these pools.
Can I have another one
for free?  Thank you.  Oh,
another one for free.
Thank you.  Oh my God.
Okay, go ahead,
raise them.  So,
we raised it from
six to eight stars
.  Uh, he got one
star, one star.  But
I'm really, really glad
we unlocked this: the
ally chain synergy plus one.
Yes.  This will make my
account stronger.  So
we're going to, uh,
put pressure on this
guy.  He gives my
cookie "Wind Spirit".
Is that his name?  This is "
Wind Archer".
Okay, I was close.
It gives the Wind
Archer critical
damage.  But we'll
remove it because it's
much better.  Where is it?
The synergy is just
crazy.  This is just
madness.  We will be
charging two units
instead of one.  So we
need to add that.  Chat.
By the way, do you see my
synergies?  If your
team doesn't look like
that, if you don't have
those synergies, then
your team
really just isn't very
good.  I made a video with a
shooting list.  You should
watch it.  This will
also help you
become a better player.
Yes.  This formation has
614,000 combat
power.  I have
649 thousand combat
power.  But I do
n't need it.  I
need 614. Yes?
Synergy is simply
better than "raw"
combat power.
Now that we've
done everything right, we've
used up all our
gold.  We
made sure everything was
pumped as well.  We
made appeals.  We
got another
pet.  Let's try again
and see
what happens.  In fact, have
we used all
our gold?  Yes,
they used it.  Okay,
we're getting a little
stuck here.  I
need serious
damage.  Okay, like this.    We
barely made it.  6
seconds.  Will go.  Yes.
The difference is 6 seconds.
Here's how it's done.
Literally
make sure
your cookies are
pumped.
Make sure
you have a synergistic
team, not just a
bunch of random
characters with high
combat power, because
half of them are
just tanks that
do nothing.
Make sure
you have buffs, healers,
defense debuffs,
basic DDs, and
pets.  Make sure
your pets
are appropriate.  Don't
just put your
pet on the car, because
he'll probably
put this
guy on it.  He's not bad
, right?  Attack percentage
is good, but there
may be things on your account that
would be a
better choice for you.  And
if you didn't
understand anything from this
video, this
"build" tab is
the most important for the
progress of your
account.  And this is gold.
This is literally gold.
Another thing is
equipment.  And there is
this.  It's called
"
equipment coverage."  You
unlock this around
level 10.  Like,
I'm supposed to be here on
mission 1035, level
8:30.  And I'm on the 600th, bro.  I
play it just as an
"idler".  I don't click
on these things.  And I
try, you know,
but I just don't do
it.  But if
you can—this is
equipment coverage.  This
will also make your account
stronger.  One more
thing: scrolling through
these features
will also boost your
account.  For me, I
choose everything that has attack
, critical chance, or
critical damage.
Honestly, I could
remove this attack and
put
damage reduction, or even
skill speed or
skill boost.
Yes, seriously, I think
so.  Put a
skill boost.
Try to find
better gear
for your account.
Also, be careful about
just
clinging to the
highest level
you've unlocked,
such as "epic."
I'm
using
magic right now, you know?
Because levels are also tied to this
equipment
.
It's not just about
rarity.  So
lower
rarity but higher
level gear may be
more useful for
your account.  One more
point: you have to
be careful,
especially with this auto-
selection.  You may
lose the best
features.  This
combat
power indicator—it simply
sums up HP, defense, and
evasion.  It's just a
collection of all
the stats, and
half of them
don't really
matter to a
regular unit.
I, for example, don't
care about his
crit resistance.  And I don't care
about his
damage reduction.  I don't
care about his
evasion rate.
Like, there are a whole bunch of
stats that are
n't really important
for certain units,
but they're lumped into
one big number.
So you might have a
bunch of just useless
features.
This one, for example, has a
lower critical chance, so
we won't
change it, right?  There is a
double critical chance here.
But there is a critical
flaw here.  So if I
wanted to, if I was
confident in the
crit chance level of all
my characters, I would
replace that.  Why?  Because
this is a direct bonus to
damage.  This is the gateway to
increased damage.
If the gate is already
wide open,
I don't need it to
be any wider,
right?  They are already
open.  So I would
want harm then, right?
But you say: "Soul,
but the strength indicator is
falling."  You are already
adults.  Okay, let's be
sensible, okay?  You have a
100% critical chance.  You don't
need more.  You're
just...you're doing
too much.  You're just
doing too much.  So,
yes, that's what I
recommend.  Oh, [ __ ],
I just clicked.
So, yes, I am inattentive
.  Anyway, I
think that's it.
Click on all the
red dots,
take all
the resources and just
tear.  We won't lose
100 attack units.
Do you know what this is?
I don't need that
crit chance.  But yes, that's
actually how you
get stronger.
This is how you get
through difficulties.  If
I missed anything,
let me know.  And of course,
don't be stupid.
Needless to say,
all it takes is a
simple swipe of a
credit card.
Of course.  Of course.
Spend money.  This
will make the game easier.
But don't be an
idiot by buying
nonsense.  Okay.
Half of the store
is complete junk.    I won't
lie to you.  I
didn't buy half the
things here.  I probably
bought a 10-piece, Emma.
Most of them were $
0.99 or $1.99.
So just
focus, chat.
Please
concentrate.  Also
join the Discord
server.  See
you later.  See you later
.